

Abhijeet Kumar Khatri

CA Semi-Qualified | B.Com(H)

An independent and self-motivated accountant with proven and tested accounting, auditing and taxation skills. More than eight years of experience in service and trading industry. Involved in the bookkeeping(R2R) to monthly closing & MIS to yearly closing and completing the audit of MNC clients.

≥ abhijeetkhatri004@gmail.com

9717926295

Oelhi, India

in linkedin.com/in/abhijeet-khatri-18624812b

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior Finance Executive

Sannam S4 Consulting Private Limited

02/2019 - Present Delhi, India

Working as consultants for MNC clients involved in service and trading activities

Duties & Responsibilities

- Accounting: Bookkeeping(R2R), MIS, Cash flow statement,
 Intercompany accounting, Fixed assets register, Payroll processing,
 Import & CHA work, A1&A2 payments, Employee reimbursements,
 Accrual & Prepaid work, deferred revenue, Ad-hoc activity etc.
- Taxation & Compliance :- TDS, TCS, 26AS, GST return, GSTR-2A Reconciliation, ARFLA, 15CA & 15CB etc.
- Audit: Co-ordination and supporting to auditor (Big-4) in Statutory Audit, Tax Audit and GST Audit etc.
- Reconciliation: Reconciliation of inter company/branch accounts, bank statements, Accounts payables, Account receivables, debtor ageing etc.
- Inventory :- Sales invoice & e-way bill, margin report, Inventory movement tracking etc.

Senior Finance Executive

Meyer Housewares India Private Limited 🗷

02/2018 - 02/2019 Delhi, India

Duties & Responsibilities

- R2R, MIS, Interbranch accounting, Fixed assets register, Import & CHA work etc.
- TDS, TCS, 26AS, GSTR, GSTR-2A Reconciliation etc.
- Supported in Statutory & Tax Audit.
- Reconciliation of inter branch accounts, bank statements, Accounts payables, Account receivables, debtor ageing, employee reimbursements etc.
- Tax invoice, E-way bill, inventory management, warehouse visit etc.

Accountant cum Article Assistant

Davinder H. Singh & Co. 🗷

07/2013 - 02/2018

Delhi, India

Duties & Responsibilities

- Prepared the service tax return, D-Vat return, GST return, TDS return etc.
- Prepared & finalized the books of accounts of all types of clients, audit reports, issuance of state forms(C/F/H forms) etc.
- Visiting to various departments for closing the pending cases, releasing the refunds, getting the registration certificates etc.

SKILLS



EDUCATION

CA Semi-Qualified

The Institute of Chartered Accountants of India

01/2012 - 11/2013 Delhi, India

B.Com (Hons)

B.R.A. Bihar University 🗗

04/2010 - 03/2013 Bihar, India

INTERESTS

Sudoku Travelling Cooking

Listening Song